<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CareerMatcher Pro</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--privacy policy text-->
    <string name="first_heading"><b>Privacy Policy for Trip Tour Guide</b>\nAt Trip Tour Guide, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Trodev and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</string>
    <string name="second_heading"><b>\nLog Files</b>\nTrip Tour Guide follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they use app. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the app, tracking users\' movement on the app, and gathering demographic information.</string>
    <string name="third_heading"><b>\nPrivacy Policies</b>\nYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Trip Tour Guide. Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Trip Tour Guide. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on this app or other apps or websites. Note that Daily Ayah has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</string>
    <string name="fourth_heading"><b>\nThird Party Privacy Policies</b>\nTrodev\'s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.</string>
    <string name="fifth_heading"><b>\nChildren\'s Information</b>\nAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Trip Tour Guide does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our App, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</string>
    <string name="sixth_heading"><b>\nConsent</b>\nBy using our app, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="google_map_key">AIzaSyB_qsP8AOP_P0MdlPz-48TDaJYjTP3vbjo</string>

    <string name="start">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="cv_header">ЁЯСЙЁЯСЙ CV ржорзЗржХрж╛рж░рзЗ ржЖржкржирж╛ржХрзЗ рж╕рзНржмрж╛ржЧрждржо!! </string>
    <string name="cv_price">ЁЯТ╕ЁЯТ╕ ржЖржорж╛ржжрзЗрж░ CV ржорзЗржХрж╛рж░ ржЪрж╛рж░рзНржЬ ржорж╛рждрзНрж░ рзирзж ржЯрж╛ржХрж╛ред</string>
    <string name="cv_delivery_time">тМЪтМЪ ржЖржкржирж┐ ржПржЗ CV рзирзк ржШржгрзНржЯрж╛рж░ ржоржзрзНржп ржЖржкржирж╛рж░ G-mail ржП ржкрзЗрзЯрзЗ ржпрж╛ржмрзЗржиред</string>
    <string name="cv_string">ЁЯСЙЁЯСЙ ржЖржкржирж┐ ржпржжрж┐ ржЦрзБржм ржХржо рж╕ржорзЯрзЗ CV ржмрж╛ржирж╛рждрзЗ ржЪрж╛ржи рждрж╛рж╣рж▓рзЗ ржЖржорж░рж╛ржЗ ржжрж┐ржЪрзНржЫрж┐ ржбрж┐ржЬрж┐ржЯрж╛рж▓ CV ржорзЗржХрж╛рж░ рж╕рж┐рж╕рзНржЯрзЗржо рж╕рзБржмрж┐ржзрж╛ред ржПржЗ-ржЬржирзНржп ржЖржкржирж╛ржХрзЗ рж╕рж╛ржорж╛ржирзНржп ржЪрж╛рж░рзНржЬ ржкрж░рж┐рж╢рзЛржз ржХрж░рждрзЗ рж╣ржмрзЗред ржЖржорж╛ржжрзЗрж░ ржерзЗржХрзЗ ржкрж┐ржбрж┐ржПржл ржлрж╛ржЗрж▓ ржПржмржВ ржУрзЯрж╛рж░рзНржб ржлрж╛ржЗрж▓ ржкрж╛ржмрзЗржиред </string>
    <string name="cv_notice">ЁЯУЭ CV ржЕрж░рзНржбрж╛рж░ ржХрж░рждрзЗ рж╣рж▓рзЗ ржЖржкржирж╛ржХрзЗ ржирж┐ржорзНржорж▓рж┐ржЦрж┐ржд ржХрж┐ржЫрзБ рждржерзНржп ржжрж┐рзЯрзЗ рж╕рж╛рж╣рж╛ржпрзНржп ржХрж░рждрзЗ рж╣ржмрзЗ ЁЯУЭ </string>
    <string name="cv_payment_number">ЁЯТ░ЁЯТ░<b> ржкрзЗржорзЗржирзНржЯ ржорзЗржержб</b>ЁЯТ░ЁЯТ░\n01615257555 (ржмрж┐ржХрж╛рж╢, ржиржЧржж, рж░ржХрзЗржЯ)</string>
    <string name="copyright">┬й Copyright 2021-2023 Trodev, all right reserved.</string>

    <string name="about_us_one">Welcome to Career Matcher Pro тАУ your ultimate companion in the journey of finding your dream job! Our innovative job seeker application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive platform to explore a world of opportunities. From detailed job descriptions, captivating images, to informative PDF files, we offer an immersive experience that goes beyond traditional job search.</string>
    <string name="premium_text">Career Matcher Pro ржЖржкржирж╛ржжрзЗрж░ ржЬржирзНржп ржирж┐рзЯрзЗ ржПрж▓рзЛ ржмрж┐рж╕рж┐ржПрж╕ рж╕рж╣ рж╕ржХрж▓ рж╕рж░ржХрж╛рж░рж┐ ржЪрж╛ржХрж░рж┐ржЬрзАржмрзАржжрзЗрж░ ржкрж░рзАржХрзНрж╖рж╛рж░ ржкрзНрж░рж╕рзНрждрзБрждрж┐рж░ ржЬржирзНржп рж╕ржХрж▓ ржзрж░ржирзЗрж░ ржоржбрзЗрж▓ ржЯрзЗрж╕рзНржЯ ржПржмржВ MCQ рж╕ржорж╛ржзрж╛ржиред рж╕рзЗржЗ рж╕рж╛ржерзЗ ржирж┐рзЯрзЗ ржПрж╕рзЗржЫрзЗ рж░рж┐ржЯрзЗржи ржкрж░рзАржХрзНрж╖рж╛рж░ ржкрзНрж░рж╕рзНрждрзБрждрж┐ рж╕рж╣ рж╕ржХрж▓ ржкрж┐ржбрж┐ржПржл</string>

</resources>